lee yon e
kim yong gwan
and also Park Yoon Woo
descendant of muldu
all names and events are fictitious
any coincidences are random
drug use is a crime
which entails the destruction of personality
and also negatively affects your 7 and the environment
part-time job
Brothers Vietnamese restaurant
courier job hourly pay 15,000 won
isn't it sad
Nowadays, at least work hard for the rest of your life
but you won’t buy a house
society only takes away your chances for a good life
so what the hell
follow his rules
brother's restaurant
just work as couriers
brothers restaurant
think about it
as about retribution as about payment
for your life
delivery
file upload
it's finally done, congratulations
thank you I was paying off my student debt
thank you all thanks
I didn't do anything
that's all you understand everything
you can be like chunu
find a good job and get out of here, understood
yes we understand you
you know wolves are afraid not to go into the forest
they won't beat us
don't worry they won't touch you
brothers restaurant free parking
정우야전우
sir my little brother joon hyung
Jun hyung yes
well done
smart girl
episode 7
police
A gang of drug dealers from Southeast Asia was detained
drug distribution
carried out through hired couriers
who were subsequently killed
Will the reporter tell us more about this?
drug gang
also known as phantom
supplied prohibited drugs under the guise of food products
to Korea and Japan
in a restaurant run by a gang leader
Prohibited substances were found
large sum of cash
as well as the victim's phone number
accident that happened on the 30th
substance analysis
found in the victim's blood
accident confirmed
probable connection between the victim and the phantom
as we assume
the group lures young men to work as courier
and then kills them and sweeps them away this way
traces
cases of smuggling and drug distribution of the phantom gang
hit-and-run resulting in death
as well as leaving the scene of an accident were combined into 1 case
after the allegations were confirmed
the cases of five members of the Vietnamese group will be transferred
to the prosecutor's office for sentencing
tell me why you are being arrested
100,000,000 by the weekend
or your loved ones will find out about it
and yet
who is this
Chandhago congratulations Chandhago Chandhago
youth is fleeting
but skill is eternal
thank your commander chan
thank you you are handsome
don't start a circus
Well, now that all the scoundrels have been caught
run to write reports and bring them to me
get a good bonus and promotion
yes sir I have the honor hey boss so
leave what you need
Why are you going to work?
love awards
love to write reports too
there is a captain, let's not go to celebrate
beef well head chan
I have to eat
where are you
got it
where I can't see stay there
I want to check something
ready go to the car
what is this, look
these are photos from the blackmailer
I just made this one
that day we were caught here
what's wrong with your hands
it turns out dong hyun and his brother were not 0
you saw something you don’t remember
no
I remembered no
but it's weird
if he was with them
why did you just sit here
and then he started blackmailing us
maybe they were Phantomovites
whom the police could not catch
they would have immediately tracked us down and come for the goods
would have earned more than 100,000,000
this is someone from our circle
he promises to send it to his loved ones
and he sent the photo to his personal number
it means someone was watching us
our acquaintance may be a blackmailer
again you're worse
Sua wrote the test
tell me how can you be worse than this girl
what else do you need academy
tutors
Do you even know how much money I’ve pumped into you? I’m asking for it
stop talking about money
I hate the academy
I hate tutors
I always do just that
what exactly do you want mom
if you regret money
no need to waste money on me
throw me out who said
that I wanted to be born your daughter
yoonjinhee
I'm better off
would be sua's sister
got it
윤진이 윤진이
I'll look for the blackmailer
while you take care of the money
1 sell
how can I earn 100,000,000 alone in a couple of days
just give me your money
you have them
no
Nevons
you're kidding when you have time
did you buy a house?
Am I not going to report to you?
I'm the one who should be angry right now
and what will we do
there is a plan, we shared the profits
this money is for my husband's treatment
Why do you think I got involved in this?
the blackmailer may not return the money
I won't touch money for anything
then there is only 1 way out
I won't, I can't do it anymore
what if we don't give him money
this idiot will send our pictures to everyone
let's give him the money
there are no other options
in the meantime I'll try to figure it out
하
how come
no
I burned 10000000
what nonsense
it's a pity how and why I
and how did you survive?
what should I do
어딨어
how did you know
stop pretending
I know perfectly well
that you were here every time you left on a business trip
you
followed me
tell me
how dare you deceive me
and treat me this way
where is she
Well, where is she, where are you doing her business, come out
where are you where are you miyeon
yang miyeon
enough here just you and me
I come here
to be 1
that I don't want to be with you
I wanted to sell a little bit at a time
We will deliver immediately after the deposit has been increased
the procedure for the fact of gin is completed
thank you
how are you
we found out the owner
he died a long time ago
phone stolen
it means everything is much more complicated
who knows
Nowadays anyone can google ways to hide a number
It's easier to act illegally these days
By the way, what did they send you?
You can't even ask anymore
ok something else
call history and location of communication towers
it's worth it
2 times more expensive
okay
I'll catch him and strangle him
awesome, they knew that jinhira was spreading rumors about sua seriously
they're girlfriends
it's true yoojeong said
she's completely finished
but what kind of love they had
that's for sure
sua
I was just worried about you Yoojeong was making it all up
you look like your mother
always blaming others for everything
look at your mother
Do you think rumors about you arose out of nowhere?
red pepper paste
you wanted to get cash
Yes, the total price of the car was 65,000,000
ticking account
I told you I can't handle it
what are you doing looking for him
what do you think
it's so simple
money is also not easy to get
as I said myself
take a closer look at your surroundings
let's each give 10,000,000
what does it mean to go all out?
I could push goods here
a prosecutor I know works overtime only while high
that's why the reports are the best
says I need to try it too
Do you know how many pieces of paper we write a day?
you would become a legend
that's why Khverim calls you gone
he was born out of boredom
jokes are not his
by the way, you dumped him
he gets mad at your name
did you set him up or what?
I also somehow missed it
so we believe he's holding a grudge against me
he forgets his mistakes
but strangers never
finished
read the 3rd quarter results report
plan for us
support and minutes of the board of directors meeting
this will be your 1 board of directors
the chairman has big plans for you
but thank you you can go
where is he
James
mint is high quality
purest product
We answer 24 hours a day
damn where did you go
where are you
found
Konkhverim recognized you
I would like to know if this is true or not
you put 1 of ours in the photo
it was a thing but you know everything yourself
something happened to me
I couldn't call what's wrong
anyway
if he recognizes himself
he would have contacted his father long ago
we would have problems
you will definitely have the required amount
I'm meeting Austin next week
we need at least 5/10 percent of shares in Tu en group
to at least convince him
yes I know I know he knows
if something goes wrong
we're all finished
while you're hiding
I do everything on my own behalf
I didn't want to mess with you
you always ruin the lives of others
I'm waiting for the money until the weekend or I'm leaving, I understand
hyuk hyuk
지저분해
curse
why now
what a beast
Enso what are you doing
you look tired
what's wrong with the face
what did you do yesterday during a sleepless night with your art teacher?
what
I teach after all
I've seen a lot of things
the more you try to seem good
the more deviations creep out
and the more terrible your betrayal will be
in my eyes
that's exactly who you are
now I understand
why were you always like an eyesore?
like a hangnail
I need to get rid of you
to make me feel better
see you tomorrow
it will be fun
great, looking forward to next week
mom is home today
hungry
no you know
I'm worried about something
I'll be back soon
eat bye
who is jenha's mom
she's not one of those
who will sit
folded arms after humiliating miyeon
could have been following us
to convict in connection
but I became a witness
but why does she need money
who would refuse an extra 1,000,000
yes you can spend them in a second
who needs money more than me now?
exactly
deprive me of money
best revenge
100000000 per week
I mean she wants
for me to continue
god
maybe I should just call her
apologize and ask for forgiveness
at least once
no
the more I try to be kind
the deeper I will be trampled into the mud
what to do
stop it
how long have you been awake
really from the moment the message was received
you can really die like that
I can't sleep
and I can't eat
as soon as I
I fall asleep then I see
1 same dream
I'm the teacher
if sua finds out
then I'll die
better die now
I ask you to spare my son
I will do anything just help him
I beg you help him
Chairman Mr.
entrance
fire extinguisher
think carefully
I agree it could be
Professor Miyeon
but if not, it’s worse for us
remember a little
maybe something strange happened recently
someone showed a little more interest in you
anyone will do
expand the search scope
the report is not ready yet
we haven't found the bag yet
what did we find at kuman's place then?
it was regular ice
and there was a new look in the bag
Hyuman killed dong hyun
because the last one stole and hid the bag
and sold drugs online
the Vietnamese confessed to everything
they said that those drugs were intended for VIPs from Japan
they were transported to the Japanese a long time ago
their testimony
what to do, the Japanese informant has disappeared
Akyuman actively exercises his right to remain silent
remember what the boss said
finish this thing already
It's not a matter of turning around with us
we did everything right
the rest doesn't matter
means
the police came to you and asked different questions
questions about me and drugs yes
but
they left with nothing
I turned it well
yes I did
like me
what did I tell you
tell me everything
how many times can you repeat
why the hell did you hide it
I didn't want to hide
I was afraid that we would stop cooperation
well you're selfish
since you need money
means don't care
what will happen to others
what are you talking about
the only egoist
here you are in command and taking my money
as far as I remember
my concern is to provide the goods
but you know what else was in the agreement
if I can be more useful
we will reconsider the conditions
I do advertising and sales and even delivery
and I get 30%
where is all the money
I gave the money
intended for the treatment of the husband
and you still haven't found the blackmailer
and that the police
it's my fault too
do you know why they came to me
my phone was in your call history
it's all your fault
you already forgot
who is to blame for that situation
you switched the drugs
adon hyung I told you so
that I will persuade him
and for some reason you got distracted and now they
what
go on, you're not trying to blame me for their deaths
of course you're trying
that's what you wanted to say
exactly what is this important call
where did you spend all the money?
how much can you use me
do you think I'm blind
pretended to be caring and understanding
to continue to incite me
don't you want to
so that I can be honest
and you yourself are silent like a partisan
why is it always me
what kind of partnership is this
it's one-sided
that's what it means I'm an evil scoundrel
that he took advantage of an innocent housewife
wait a minute though
It was you who was looking for me to chat
I just wanted
since you don't like everything
do whatever you want
and I'll figure it all out
what are you going to do hey you
ok do what you want
I'll take care of everything
do you live here
this is your home
from the very beginning I didn’t want to lie
jenhee misunderstood
thinking that I live there
but I didn’t deny
lee da yoon
Song Hana Park Chi Min
kyung do here and there
the fool has finally grown up
hard workers in the department is good
you're not in the mood
he's suspicious
very addicted to drugs
who knows, he desperately wanted to find the bag
I used to run straight to my family
and now he's sitting here in his pants
you still don't understand
how phantoms kept in touch with the police
no
keep order
seriously
you really can’t even tell the girls about my house
if you return what was stolen
why are you helping me
Why are you flushed?
it's just temperature
wipe your snot
ready
sua
who is this
Isn't it a teacher by any chance?
hey
look what sua drew give me
give me the drawing
By the way, you're his favorite
you have a rival
about something he only loves me
no me he likes my drawings
you don't understand
he just wanted to motivate
everyone has a dark side
but
it doesn't define you
you
sorry and by the way
what did you deliver there?
happiness hospital
wrong password
try again in 29 seconds
try again in 15 seconds
you always pay in cash
some problems
not at all
a little short of 153,000 to pay for this week
I'll tell you tomorrow
good
I can do it myself
you will be discharged tomorrow
you will need to talk to your doctor
yeah and drag him
he as much as necessary
how do you imagine it?
after the parent meeting I will go straight to you
you have a lot to do
I can handle it myself like this
got ready to catch the bus
I mean you
insurance doesn't cover my treatment
I heard you work as a housekeeper for a teacher sua
it's true
so you pay for my treatment
dear, don't you want to tell me anything
James
I'll be right back, wait
are you serious
why did you change your account password?
you complained about the amount of work
so I decided to help
dissatisfied again
that you will receive rights for your work
From now on I will deal with delivery and customers
you will still have the packaging of the goods
why are you or give me your bag and leave
and I'm not happy with this
you
now the subscriber cannot answer your call damn
what a bastard
dropper urgently needed
call details
gwangnam area
Chuman street 12 1
Chunan street 12 1
cafe ribro
Chunam street 15 4
beef chic cafe
chunam street 19
Gwangnam District Police Station
police station
16th 0
Mina gave the police information about James
22 0 CEO Medusa James
where are you now
called on the orders of the police
police my phone was in your call history everything
you're to blame 10th 0
police came to insu's house
16th 0 Hwang brothers broke into Insoo's house
Messages found on dong hyun's phone
from the quilter
phantom informant
I spoke to the host
says minu should know james
stizhiatel call history today
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
achiever
phantom informant
policeman
this is a droper
resident card
what are you doing
you go to drawing and yes
By the way, buy me some takpacks
you don't have any money
it's your turn, let's have pork ribs instead
so now we can move on to voting
please raise your hand
who is in favor of installing CCTV cameras in classrooms
I'm over 12 too
who's against three
what then
mom sua
you're the only one
you didn't vote for or against
I think against it
we must respect children's personal space
they are very sensitive now
cameras are needed to prevent crashes
we still haven't caught the culprit
we need evidence so she can't get away with it
everything for the sake of our children
Have you heard about that recent incident?
why were the brothers selling illegal substances
even minors bought them
we adults need to keep our ears open
and control the situation
to prevent this from happening to our children
oh yes mama sua
you worked with that criminal, right?
I saw him quite often next to you in the store
such an ordinary boy
I couldn't even think
what are you getting at
yes so
the world is a scary place
It's often the people who do the worst things
just innocent lambs
so ladies
let's take a short break
maybe someone wants to go to the toilet
I guess I'll go with you
do you plan to leave it in korea
no, now many people prefer to study in Europe
great place by the way
did you know what was there
thank you this is the scent
bon appetit
enough is enough
but I didn't like it
no need, I'll put it on myself
yeah take it already
yes
thank you
let's clink glasses
we finally had a drink together
you'll be so cute
parking is prohibited
Chang Daegu divorced in '17
cause of domestic violence and failed investments
has a debt to the bank of 320,000,000
won pays monthly
father's medical expenses amounting to 8,000,000 won
does he have a motive and a reason?
need to check
hwang jongsu
I'm listening
Korean beef restaurant
ah
아
I was so scared
why are you following me?
Miyeon stop being a coward and ruining my life
say what you want
be a coward
now you talk to me like that
and you have become much bolder
or I finally lost my fear
yes
that very evening
I told you so
I need to get rid of a hangnail
means
it's really you
that's why I'm in favor of installing CCTV cameras
but I didn't plan to go that far
it's true
almost
although if you think about it
It’s better to send a photo to the girls’ chat
and not to the parent
just to be sure
yes indeed
Tujin
congratulations on your discharge
thank you no more pain
and don't come here
Happy discharge, be healthy and take care of yourself, thank you
come on in sometime
of course yangseok
and you will be discharged soon
Yes, I'll buy you a Rubik's cube, thank you
아아
아
when people are forced to face the unknown
they do things
which we couldn’t even imagine
this is how our true essence is revealed
what kind of woman are you?
what happened
can you hear me
woman
answer
currency exchange
this is how I ordered it
he asked me to break 100,000,000 into smaller amounts
apparently he is very careful
Meeting point every Thursday at 5pm
something's wrong
when the economy is in decline 1
construction and advertising business suffer
share price fell by 2 thirds
company assets are at risk
we are planning expansion
Should I panic?
now at the slightest problem
even defensive stocks will be at risk
It's better to honor the straw now
preparing for possible decline
you can only cause more price collapse
Our priority now is communication with investors
that's right mr director
啊
Korean language dictionary
Director, are you doing well?
board of directors
let's buy something to eat
Korean language dictionary
the subscriber cannot answer your call now
idiot answer it's urgent
get out of here
move image to trash to trash
where are the rest of the photos?
what's wrong with her
jinhee mom how are you
oh my god
how did that happen
she'll be fine
oh did you see her face
what a nightmare
Korean language dictionary
here he is
rod
descendant of muldu
I love the expressions on your faces
I didn't recognize you at first either
are you we need to stop now
and if you fire me
I won't have anything to live on
you want to quit
you work as a courier
how much do they pay
who is this quilter now
200,000,000 per week in cash
how did you find out the name
really
this woman is our cover, keep her with you
if anything happens we'll fall on her
translated and voiced by the studio
mobile television ordered by online cinema ivi
in 2025